SARAH MORRISON

123 Your Street New York, NY 12345 sarahrmorrison@ex.ample.com (123) 456-7890

A Computer Engineering Professional with five years of experience specializing in Python, hardware design, automation, and prototyping, A strong track record of leading the design and build-out of technology solutions to automate testing processes and enhance the efficiency of manufacturing operations for medical device corporations.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE (B.S.) COMPUTER ENGINEERING

University of Syracuse, Syracuse, NY September 2012 - May 2016

KEY SKILLS

- Computer Engineering
- Automation
- Hardware Solutions
- Prototyping
- Manufacturing

CERTIFICATIONS

- ♦ CompTIA A+, 2016
- Microsoft Certified Professional (MCP), 2016

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

COMPUTER ENGINEER MedDevice Manufacturers Inc., New York, NY May 2018 - Present

- Drive the development of automated testing and validation for hardware solutions supporting manufacturing production for a \$30M medical device company
- Coordinate with cross-functional teams across mechanical engineering, QA, firmware, and software engineering to drive process improvement and reduce production costs by 10%
- Identify solutions to manufacturing obstacles and roadblocks, including the development and implementation of new hardware and software tools

COMPUTER ENGINEER Brooklyn Tech Partners, New York, NY May 2016 - May 2018

- Support the build-out, design, and maintenance of cross-compilers and microcontrollers in embedded environments, including code reviews and bug fixes
- Coordinate with system administrators to install, maintain, and configure hardware, software, and application tools, including the delivery of system upgrades
- Interface with technical teams to identify opportunities to enhance application and system performance by conducting hardware and infrastructure upgrades